PECHORSKYKH VIKTOR

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER











ABOUT MYSELF

II have 2 years of experience creating high-quality applications, with a focus on solving complex tasks and generating effective ideas. My exceptional responsibility and motivation set me apart, helping me develop professional skills and stay at the forefront of modern technologies. I easily adapt to teamwork and am also able to work productively on my own.

I am committed to continuous learning and selfimprovement, always seeking new opportunities to expand my knowledge and experience in the tech field. I have strong skills in quickly finding and analyzing information, allowing me to stay up-to-date with the latest trends and technologies.

EXPERIENCE

02/2023-10/2024

Full Stack Developer in an outsourcing company.

Developed and maintained web applications, ensuring high performance, scalability, and responsiveness by utilizing modern frameworks and technologies. Collaborated with cross-functional teams to design, implement, and deploy user-friendly interfaces and efficient backend solutions. Debugged and optimized code to enhance application performance and user experience. Integrated third-party APIs and services to extend application functionality.

2023-Present

Freelance. Development of e-commerce platforms and portfolio websites using the MERN stack.

2021-2023

Head of the Legal Department at a construction company.

Led a team of lawyers, coordinated the legal support processes for transactions, and represented the company's interests in negotiations. Ensured compliance with all legal requirements at various stages of construction projects, minimizing risks and contributing to the effective execution of business objectives.

2019-2021

Lawyer. Responsible for preparing claims, managing contract work, and providing legal support for cases.

LANGUAGES

- English B2
- German B2
- Ukrainian native
- · Russian native

SKILLS

- Languages: JavaScript | TypeScript | PHP | Python
- Frontend Development: HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | TypeScript | React.js | Next.js | Redux Toolkit | Zod | Zustand | React Hook Form | Joi | Yup | Tailwind CSS | Sass | Recharts.js | Vue.js | Angular | Dnd-kit | MUI | React Bootstrap | Apollo GraphQL | Clerk | Okta
- 💻 Backend Development: Node.js | Express.js | Nest.js | RESTful APIs | Laravel | Django | GraphQL | Prisma | Sequelize | TypeORM | MongoDB/Mongoose | Websockets | Microservices | PostgreSQL | MySQL
- Mobile Development: React Native | Expo
- Responsive Web Design
- Testing and Debugging: Vitest | Jest | RTL | StoryBook | Playwright
- Control: Git
- ♦ Other: socket.io | RegEx | axios | i18next
- Tools: Docker | Figma | Adobe XD | Sketch | SonarQube | Robo 3T | OWASP ZAP | BrowserStack
- 💻 Visual Studio Code | Webpack | MongoDB Compass | PgAdmin | Chrome DevTools | Redux Devtools | npm | yarn | pnpm | nvm | ESLint | Prettier | Linux | GitHub | GitLab | AWS | Swagger | Xcode

EDUCATION

2020-2022

Computer science (Educational program: Systems and methods of artificial intelligence), Bachelor's degree -National Technical University of Ukraine "Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute"

2016-2020

Law, Bachelor's degree - Academy of Advocacy of Ukraine

2020-2022

Law, Master's degree - Academy of Advocacy of Ukraine

2022-2024

Psychology, Master's degree - European University